Alumni Memorabilia; Collection ua801.004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
University at Albany, SUNY Alumni Memorabilia Collection
1845-2014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua801.004
12.21 cubic ft. 917 Digital Files processed to date
The collection documents the day-to-day student life at the University at Albany and its predecessor institutions, including the State Normal School (1844-1890), the New York State Normal College (1890-1914), the New York State College for Teachers (1914-1959), and the State University of New York at Albany (1962-1986).
Historical Note
The Alumni Association collected information on graduates as well as memorabilia of alumni since its founding in 1849. Unfortunately, the devastating New York State Normal College fire of January 8, 1906 destroyed those early collections as it did the portraits of early school leaders and the Alumni Memorial Window in the Willett Street Building. In consequence there are relatively few items of memorabilia in the collection from the 19th Century, and what is known about the graduates of the New York State Normal School and the New York State Normal College through 1906 is largely found in the Historical Sketch of the State Normal School, 1884 and the Historical Sketch of the State Normal College, 1894. A hand annotated copy of the 1894 history was maintained by the Alumni Association with interleaved pages and contains updates to the names, addresses and careers of graduates of the Normal School/College (1844-1914), and subsequently the New York State College for Teachers (1914-1959) through 1918.
During the 1910s through the 1950s alumni have been particularly generous with donating their memorabilia, scrapbooks, play programs, photos of events such as Rivalry, Moving Up Day, commencements, plays, fraternities and sororities, and the general round of social life. With the advent of the 1960s there has been a significant diminution of alumni donation of memorabilia, and while many classes during the 1920s-1940s have upwards of a hundred individual items of memorabilia, very few approach that number in later years, often numbering the teens or twenties.
In 1988 the University Archives took over custodianship of the Alumni Memorabilia Collection from the Alumni Association.
Scope and Contents
Items in this collection have been transferred to the Alumni Association of the University at Albany, SUNY for the past 100 years. The collection consists of autograph books, broken runs of bulletins, catalogues, and commencement exercises; the correspondence of alumni, faculty and students; newspaper clippings; photographs of alumni, faculty, students, student events and buildings; programs for student and local plays; programs of college and student events, scrap books, song books, student literary publications and yearbooks. The collection documents the day-to-day student life at the University at Albany and its predecessor institutions: the State Normal School, 1844-1890; the New York State Normal College, 1890-1914; the New York State College for Teachers, 1914-1959; the State University of New York College of Education at Albany, 1959-61; the State University of New York College at Albany, 1961-62; and the State University of New York at Albany, 1962-1986.
Though the span date of the collection is 1844 through 1991, there are few items before 1860. The nineteenth century materials consist primarily of formal portrait photographs of students and faculty; autograph books from 1860, 1861, and 1889 (autograph books were the forerunners of college yearbooks--see the University Archives Autograph Book Collection for more extensive examples of the genre); scattered commencement exercises and diplomas (see the University Archives Diploma Collection and Commencement Series for other examples); the correspondence of Anna E. Pierce, a graduate of the Class of 1884, and future Dean of Women; and the papers of Carolyn Mayhew, a graduate of the Class of 1892, and assistant school principal in New York City (including her essays and an autobiographical book Life on A Diary Farm in the Nineteenth Century).
The twentieth century holdings of the collection are much richer, consisting, in addition to the usual commencement programs and photographs, of a variety of regalia including athletic letters from 1927; womens basketball memorabilia donated by Lorna Shafer including a list of rules of personal conduct of women athletes; candle holders used on Torch Night and Candlelight Ceremony; dance cards; felt arm bands from the classes of 1913, 1918, 1921, 1923, 1924, 1926, 1935, 1937, 1949; play programs, particularly from the period when Agnes Futterer lead theatrical programming (1918-1956), as well as programs for events held at local and New York City theaters; school pins from fraternities, sororities, and MYSKANIA (the student honorary and guardian of traditions); scrap books from members of the class of 1923, 1926, 1929, 1933, 1939, 1942, 1943, 1949; song books; student literary and humor magazines; tea pots from Syddum Hall; women's gym rompers dating from 1927 and 1937.
The collection is strongest in the period from 1920 through the mid-1950s and weakest before and after those dates. With notable exceptions, primarily scattered copies of student publications, the Alumni Memorabilia Collection contains few items from the 1960s on.
The Alumni Memorabilia Collection exists 1) to provide a repository for items which can be exhibited at Alumni Reunions, Homecoming and in the wider University community, and 2) to provide a mechanism by which the University Archives can document student life at the University and its predecessor institutions. To achieve these goals we solicit donations which are attractive, colorful and/or informative, and at the same time we collect materials which will give us insight into student life, both in and outside of classes.
University Archives plans to add new class memorabilia to this finding aid on an annual basis.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into series by donor's graduating class. If the donor is unknown, the item is arranged by creation date. More series will be processed over time.
Acquisition Information
The materials in this collection were donated by alumni of the University at Albany and its predecessor institutions: the State Normal School, 1844-1890; the New York State Normal College, 1890-1914; the New York State College for Teachers, 1914-1959; the State University of New York College of Education at Albany, 1959-61; the State University of New York College at Albany, 1961-62; and the State University of New York at Albany, 1962-1986.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
State University of New York at Albany--History; Graduation (School)--New York(State)--Albany; College student newspapers and periodicals--New York (State)--Albany; College student orientation--United States--Handbooks, manuals, etc.; College students--New York (State)--Albany; College students--Political activity--New York (State)--Albany; College students--Recreation--New York (State)--Albany; Programs (documents); Invitations; Dance cards; Photographs; Newspapers; School yearbooks; Memorabilia; Hats; Pennants; Digital Files; UAlbany Student Groups; State University of New York at Albany
- Class of 1879
  - Henry L. Taylor scrapbook, 1879 June 27
- Class of 1936, 1932; 1936
  - The State College Music Association Pianoforte Recital by Percy Grainger, Program, 1932 October 21
  - Newspaper clipping titled, "Percy Grainger's Recital Transfixes his Audience", 1932
- Class of 1938, 1937; 1938
  - Program from the State College Music Association titled, "Concert by the State College Choral Society and Percy Grainger, Pianist", 1937 January 21
- Class of 1945, 1929-1998; 1945
  - State College Songbook, 1929 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 1)
  - Basketball Schedule 1941-1942 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 2)
  - Samuel C. Dickieson Scrapbook (photocopies and a cover letter), 1941 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 3)
  - State College Directory 1941-1942 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 4)
  - Flyer for Freshman Camp for Women at Camp Van Schoonhaven, Burden Lake, N.Y., 1941 September 12-14 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 5)
  - Program for State College Music Association presents Jaques Fray and Mario Braggiotti, duo-pianists, at Albany High School Auditorium, 1941 October 15 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 6)
  - Music Association program featuring duo-pianists Jaques Fray and Mario Braggiotti, 1941 October 15 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 7)
  - New York State College for Teachers Women's Athletic Association Handbook 1941-1942 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 8)
  - Program for Dramatics and Art Association presents Three One-Act Plays at Page Hall, 1942 January 13 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 9)
  - Program for Music Association presents Gilbert and Sullivan's comedic opera Pirates of Penzance at Page Hall Auditorium, 1942 April 23-24 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 10)
  - Program for Advanced Dramatics play, The Royal Family at Page Hall, 1942 May 15 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 11)
  - Program for the State College Music Association presents the Don Cossack Chrous at Page Hall Auditorium, 1943 February 27 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 12)
  - Program for State College Music Association Concert by the State College Women's Chorus and Percy Grainger, 1943 May 8 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 13)
  - Program for Ladies in Retirement at Page Hall Auditorium, 1943 May 21 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 14)
  - Program for Music Council presents Conrad Thibault, Baritone, accompanied by Alderson Mowbray at Page Hall Auditorium, 1943 October 15 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 15)
  - State College Directory 1944-1945 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 16)
  - Textbook - Geographic Education Series: Map Reading, 1944 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 17)
  - Photograph of Myskunia, copy of UA #3862, 1944 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 18)
  - Program for Tommorow's Teachers, 1944 May 5 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clipping, "Mary Now is Crowned Queen at State College", 1944 October 15 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 20)
  - Program - Ruth Draper, State College Dramatic Arts Council, 1944 October 20 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 21)
  - Program - The Damask Cheek, 1944 December 9 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 22)
  - Report of the Committee on the Peculiar Excellence of the College, a Committee of the Faculty Council, 1945 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 23)
  - 2 pins - Gold Pi Gamma Mu Pin, Silver Sword Pin Newman Hall Graduation Pin, 1945 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 24)
  - Silver Sword Pin, Gift to Newman Hall Graduates, 1945 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 25)
  - The College Research Paper by Louis C. Jones and William G. Hardy, 1945 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 26)
  - "The House Divided," "Overtones," "Why I am a Bachelor" program at Page Hall Auditorium [2 copies], 1945 January 16 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 27)
  - The Chimes of Normandy program, 1945 March 22-23 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 28)
  - The Primer, 1945 May (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 29)
  - Night Must Fall program, 1945 May 25-26 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 30)
  - Textbook - The College Research Paper: Simplified Prodecure, 1946 March 2 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 31)
  - Letter and Postcard from Biology Professor Gertrude Douglas to Louise Stone '45 and Gertrude Douglas Obituary, 1948; 1949; Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 32)
  - Reunion Responses, 1990 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 33)
  - 45th Reunion Program, 1990 June 9 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 34)
  - 50th Reunion tags, 1995 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 35)
  - Reminiscences of Sayles Hall 1941-1942, ca. 1998 (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 36)
  - Felt Arm Bands for the Class of '45, Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 37)
  - Song Sheets, Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 38)
  - Small red "1945" ribbon, Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 39)
  - The Statesmen, Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 40)
  - The Statesmen, Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 41)
  - Note from Mrs. "Mac" to Louise Stone '45, asking Louise to greet guests for dinner at dining room, including Mrs. Sayles, Undated (Box 1 (1945-Class of 1945), Folder 42)
- Class of 1949, 1941-2014; 1949
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  On Monday, June 20, 1949 approximately 300 members of the Class of 1949 received their bachelor's degrees during a morning ceremony in Page Hall. Alvin Christian Eurich, president, State University of New York, served as commencement speaker and conferred the degrees. In the days leading to commencement, the class held a Senior Banquet at Herbert's, a Senior Ball at the Aurania Club, Class Day Exercises at Page Hall followed that evening by the Class Sing and Torchlight Procession at Draper Hall, and finally, a senior breakfast on the morning of graduation at the Boulevard Cafeteria.
  During the Class of 1949's tenure on campus, New York State College for Teachers President John Sayles resigned in March 1947 because of ill health and was replaced by Acting President Milton Nelson who held the position until July 1949. The College officially became part of the newly created State University of New York on April 1, 1949. In addition, in May 1949, the student body selected the Pedguin, a penguin-like figure designed by Paul Kirsch '51, as the official College mascot.
  There is a significant amount of memorabilia from the Class of 1949 including yearbooks, event programs, materials from Senior Week and commencement exercises, handbooks, directories, and many materials from reunions. Of particular interest may be the scrapbooks from Elfriede Laemmerzahl Miller, Margaret Hoefner Baynes and Lucy Lytle Merrill documenting student life from 1945-1949. Miller's scrapbook includes the program for Frosh Weekend 1945 and Freshman Week as well as her freshman beanie and upperclass red hat. Merril's scrapbook contains a large number of photographs including classmates and campus events. Baynes' three scrapbooks include many tickets and special event programs.
  - Lucy Lytle's Elementary and Secondary Certificates, 1941; 1945 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 1)
  - Class of 1949 Freshman Handbook, 1945 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 2)
  - Primer, 1945-1947 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 3)
  - Elfriede Laemmerzahl Miller's College Scrapbook, 1945-1949 (Oversized 1)
  - Lucy Lytle Merrill's College Scrapbook, 1945-1949 (Oversized 2)
  - Lucy Lytle's Notebooks Recording her Finances During College, 1945-1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 4)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory, 1945-1950 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 5)
  - Spring Concert, Music Council NYSCT Program, 1946 May 17 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 6)
  - State College News, 1946 September-1946 November (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 7)
  - Pedagogue Yearbook, 1946 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 8)
  - Margaret Hoefner Baynes' College Scrapbook, 1946-1947 (Oversized 3)
  - Pearl Primus and Group Program, 1947 February 05 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 9)
  - "The Powdered Wig" Program, 1947 March 01 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 10)
  - "Ermine" Program, 1947 March 2-21 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 11)
  - "And Four to Go" Program, Presented by Sophomore Class, 1947 March 29 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 12)
  - Folk Festival, Inter-Group Council, 1947 April 19 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 13)
  - State College News Coverage of Student Association Elections, 1947 May 09 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 14)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner" Program, 1947 May 23-1947 May 24 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 15)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday Program, 1947 June 15 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 16)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1947 June 16 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 17)
  - State College News Vol. XXXII, No. 1, 1947 September 19 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 18)
  - Registration Procedure, 1947 September (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 19)
  - State College News Vol. XXXII, No. 4, 1947 October 10 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 20)
  - State College Christmas Formal, 1947 December 13 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 21)
  - Office of the President, Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 22)
  - Photograph of Sigma Lambda Sigma Fraternity, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 23)
  - Student Association Card, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 24)
  - Primer, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 25)
  - Student Receipts, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 26)
  - Elementary Dramatics, Three One Act Plays, "The Kelly Kid," "The Ugly Duckling," and "The Doctor's Duty" Program, 1948 January 13 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 27)
  - Ticket to Junior Class Banquet, 1948 February 07 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 28)
  - Official Catalogue, New York State College for Teachers, Vol. XLIII, No. 1, 1948 February 28 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 29)
  - "HMS Pinafore" Program, 1948 March 12-1948 March 13 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 30)
  - Class of 1948 Commencement Exercises Program, 1948 June 14 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 31)
  - Class of 1949 Moving Up Day Arm Band, 1948 June (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 32-34)
  - Registration Procedure, 1948 September (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 35)
  - Albany Times-Union Clipping of Phi-Delta Tea, 1948 November 14 (Flat-file 1)
  - Lecture - Concert by Milton Cross, 1948 December 02 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 36)
  - Interfraternity-Intersorority of NYSCT, Christmas Formal Program/Dance Card, 1948 December 10 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 37)
  - NYSCT Christmas Formal Souvenir with Photograph, 1948 December 10 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 38)
  - Holiday Time, Presented by Hillel, Newman Club, Student Christian Association, 1948 December 15 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 39)
  - "Our Fourteen Points" 1948 Platform of the Socialist Party of the State of New York (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 40)
  - Pedagogue Yearbook with Inscriptions, 1948 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 41)
  - Margaret Hoefner Correspondence, 1948; Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 42)
  - United Nations, 1948; Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 43)
  - Margaret Hoefner Baynes' College Scrapbooks, 1948-1949 (Oversized 3-4)
  - Bunter Abend, 1949 January 07 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 44)
  - Faculty Arts Exhibition, 1949 February 14-1949 February 18 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 45)
  - Student Religious Clubs Clipping, "Cupid's Hope", 1949 February (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 46)
  - "The Pirates of Penzance" Program, 1949 March 11-1949 March 12 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 47)
  - "For Heaven's Sake" Program, 1949 March 26 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 48)
  - State College News April Fools Issue, 1949 April 01 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 49)
  - "Lucky Number" Program, 1949 April 09 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 50)
  - State College News Coverage of Student Association Elections, 1949 May 07 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 51)
  - Spring Concert, Music Council NYSCT Program, 1949 May 13 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 52)
  - "The Corn is Green" Program, 1949 May 20-1949 May 21 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 53)
  - Social Studies Seminar, 1949 May 26 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 54)
  - Letter to Seniors from Bertha E. Brimmer and Olive H. McDermott Regarding Alumni Association, 1949 June 06 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 55)
  - Class of 1949 Senior Ball Program, 1949 June 17 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 56)
  - Ticket to Senior Ball at the Aurania Club, 1949 June 17 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 57)
  - Alumni Day Special Centennial Program, 1949 June 18 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 58)
  - Invitation to the President's Reception, 1949 June 18 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 59)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday Program, 1949 June 19 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 60)
  - Announcement of Commencement Exercises, 1949 June 20 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 61)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1949 June 20 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 62)
  - Bachelor of Arts Diploma of Lucy Lytle, 1949 June 20 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 63)
  - Albany Times-Union Clipping of Class of 1949 Commencement, 1949 June (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 64)
  - Class of 1949, Order of Exercises Leading to Commencement, 1949 June (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 65)
  - Office of the Registrar, Diploma Instructions, ca. June 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 66)
  - Alumni Association Newsletter, "Our First 100 Years", 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 67)
  - Class Night Instructions, 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 68)
  - Holiday Inn, Sigma Lambda Sigma Formal, 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 69)
  - Pedagogue Yearbook with Inscriptions, 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 70)
  - Boulevard "Grill" Menu (Photocopy) and Ticket, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 71)
  - "Captain" Red Ribbon, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 72)
  - MYSKANIA Key of Barbara Hope Houck with list of 1950 MYSKANIA Members, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 73)
  - "NYSCT-Class of 1949" Empty Booklet, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 74)
  - Phi Delta Namecard with the Name "Annette", ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 75)
  - Red Construction Paper Devil, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 76)
  - "Smiles" and Picnic Ticket, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 77)
  - State '49 Patch, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 78)
  - Studenten Spiegel with Sketches of Faculty and Students Possibly by William G. Meyer, ca. 1949 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 79)
  - Lucy Lytle's Teaching Certificate and Licenses, 1950-1953 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 80)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1952 June 15 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 81)
  - Master of Arts Diploma for Lucy Lytle, 1952 June 15 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 82)
  - Arena Theater Program "The Moon is Blue", 1953 July 09-1953 July 11 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 83)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1954 June 13 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 84)
  - Alumni Day Tag of Annette DeLyser, 1955 June 11 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 85)
  - Class of 1955 Commencement Ticket, 1955 June 12 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 86)
  - Class of 1949 35th Reunion Program, 1984 May 12 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 87)
  - Alumni Day Program, 1989 June 03 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 88)
  - Invitation to 40th Class Reunion, 1989 June 03 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 89)
  - Class of 1949 Reunion Photographs, 1989; 1994 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 90)
  - Class of 1949 45th Reunion Photographs, 1949 June 10 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 91)
  - Class of 1949 Photograph and Badge from 45th Reunion, 1949 June 10 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 92)
  - Class of 1949 45th Reunion Program, 1949 June 10 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 93)
  - Reunion Scrapbook, 1979; 1984; 1994; 1999 (Oversized 5)